
{"question":"excuse me", "answer": "undskyld"}
{"question": "yes", "answer": "ja"}
{"question":"a little","answer":"lidt"}
{"question": "goodbye", "answer":"farvel"}
{"question":"a coffee","answer":"en kaffe"}
{"question":"thank you","answer":"tak"}
{"question":"really","answer":"virkelig"}
{"question":"apple","answer":"Ã¦ble"}
{"question":"woman", "answer":"kvinden"}
{"question":"girl", "answer":"pige"}
{"question":"she","answer":"hun"}
{"question":"man","answer":"mand"}
{"question":"boy","answer":"dreng"}
{"question":"he","answer":"han"}
{"question":"is","answer":"er"}
{"question":"a","answer":"en"}
{"question":"you","answer":"du"}
